<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ev1lm0rty</title>
    <link>https://ev1lm0rty.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ev1lm0rty</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Shubham Arya</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 14:05:55 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ev1lm0rty.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shell Tips and Tricks</title>
      <link>https://ev1lm0rty.com/posts/shell-tips-and-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 14:05:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ev1lm0rty.com/posts/shell-tips-and-tricks/</guid>
      <description>About Hi readers, it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since my last blog. I&amp;rsquo;m not used to blogging regularly, but anyways, I&amp;rsquo;m trying to keep up. So today I&amp;rsquo;ll share some shell tips and tricks that I discoverd/read/picked-up-from-the-internet/learned-from-my-friends so that you can make your life easier too.
Tips 1. Copy text from your shell to your clipboard. Hate to select text manually from the terminal ? I feel you, here&amp;rsquo;s how you can do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book-Summary: The Miracle Morning</title>
      <link>https://ev1lm0rty.com/posts/the-miracle-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 17:33:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ev1lm0rty.com/posts/the-miracle-morning/</guid>
      <description>Wake up early at the same time every day You can achieve level 10 success in every field Follow life S.A.V.E.R.S every morning  S: Silence A: Affirmations V: Visualizations E: Exercise R: Read S: Scribe   &amp;ldquo;Your self talk has powerful impact on your success in each field.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Whether you think you can or you think you can&amp;rsquo;t, you are right.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;You can use affirmations to start programming yourself to be confident and successful in everything you do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book-Summary: The Psychology of Money</title>
      <link>https://ev1lm0rty.com/posts/the-psychology-of-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 17:27:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ev1lm0rty.com/posts/the-psychology-of-money/</guid>
      <description>Most money decisions are made by personal experiences. Something that makes sense to one, might sound crazy to another. We don&amp;rsquo;t have much data/experience with money and we are just working with our experiences. &amp;ldquo;I want you to be successful, and I want you to earn it. But realize that not all success is due to hard work, and not all poverty is due to laziness. Keep this in mind while judging people, including yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Log4j (The skiddie way)</title>
      <link>https://ev1lm0rty.com/posts/find-log4j/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 17:17:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ev1lm0rty.com/posts/find-log4j/</guid>
      <description>About So the past week the internet was on fire, log4j CVE dropped and it dropped hard. It was like as if people were running for their lives, putting out fires. And it got even worse after the infosec community quickly started hunting for this vulnerability. Today let’s take a dig into vulnerability and learn how to find it (The skiddie way).
What is Log4j CVE-2021-44228 I guess you already know about it, if not then here are some great resources:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
